(Bernadette:)into the Rhesus monkey lab.
(Bernadette:)Besides, Penny and I are having
a girls' night tonight.
(Amy:)Girls' night?
What does that entail?
(Bernadette:)Oh, you know, girls get
together,
(Bernadette:)hang out, share girl talk.
(Amy:)I'm a girl.
(Bernadette:)Oh. Well, maybe you can join us.
I'll ask Penny.
(Amy:)No need. Penny and I
are very close.
(Bernadette:)You are?
(Amy:)Yes. In fact,
our menses are synchronized.
(Howard:)Penny.
(Amy:)Bernadette tells me you're
planning a girls' night.
(Penny:)Yeah?
(Amy:)I'm a girl.
(Penny:)Oh. Um, it was-- it was just
going to be me and Bernadette.
(Penny:)Besides, I thought you
were going to the movies
(Penny:)with Sheldon and the guys.
(Amy:)Yes, but they're not girls.
(Amy:)I'm a girl.
(Penny:)Yeah, no, no,
I-I-I got that.
(Amy:)What's the dress code?
(Penny:)Uh, just wear something
comfortable.
(Amy:)All right.
I'll have to go shopping.